Seward, Ralph T. Papers 5328
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
2294712
- Series I: Arbitration Cases, General
  - S.U.B. Rights to Sub Benefits during the 1959 Strike, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Air Line Pilots Association International and United Air Lines, Inc. Davidson and Cosgrave Grievances, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alco Products, Inc. United Steelworkers Local 4942 (Formerly American Locomotive) Grievance No. 29, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel Corporation United Steelworkers Local 1138 No. 6 Ram Tractor; Nos. 1-5-10 Rams and No. 26 Fork Tractor, and No. 1 Tow and No. 3 Platform Tractors, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation United Steelworkers Local 1196 Brackenridge Plant - Gr. 8-2 Dept., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allegheny Ludlum SteelCo. (Brackenridge Plant) & U.S.A. Grievance. # CL-1-57 & CL-2-57, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alleghany-Ludlum - Brackenridge, Pa. United Steelworkers - Local 1196 Gr. # 2758, heard 4/16/56, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alleghany-Ludlum - Brackenridge, Pa. United Steelworkers - Local 1196 Gr. # 2778, heard 4/16/56, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allegheny Ludlum, Brackenridge Plant United Steelworkers, Local No. 1196 Grievance No. 2666. Decision 10-9-54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ALSC - Brackenridge Plant - Local 1196 Grievance No. 2480 6/21/50, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Workers Association of America Pensioner J. Roski 11/23/59, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Allegheny Ludlum, Dunkirk United Steelworkers, Local #2693 Job Classification: 12-7-54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allegheny Ludlum, Dunkirk United Steelworkers, Local #2693 Grievance No. 53:181 12-7-54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. Dunkirk United Steelworkers, Local No. 2639 Grievance No. 53:181 12/6/54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. Classification Case Dunkirk 12/6/54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Allegheny Ludlum. Leechburg United Steelworkers, (#1 Shearing) 3-4-55 #1138 - 6-8-55, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Allegheny Ludlum - Leechburg Plant United Steelworkers Local # Hearing 2-1-55, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allegheny-Ludlum - West Leechburg United Steelworkers - Local 1138 No. 5 Welding Line 5/31/55, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ALSC - Leechburg Plant - Local 1138 Grievance No. 19-H, 22-H, & 25-H, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ALSC - West Leechburg Plant - Local 1138 - Grievance No. 24-H 6/21/50, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - American Bridge Division (U.S. Steel )United Steelworker # 1117 Grievance No. A-58-16 (Gary Plant), 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American Bridge Div. United States Steel Corp. and United Steelworkers (3 Grievances), 1952-1958 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Chain & Cable Co. and U.S.A., Local No. 2715, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Locomotive Schenectady United Steelworkers - Local 2054, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Radiator - Youngstown Kitch., Gr. No. H-56-8, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corporation - 7/6/52 Grievance of Roy C. Gentry, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - American Bridge Company - Local 1270 Ambridge Plant - Grievances A-49-72 A-49-74--78. 82. 84, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Company Brief American Bridge Division, United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local #1579 - Shiffler Plant 9/21/56 Grievances A-56-4, A-56-6, A-56-7, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - American Bridge Company vs. United Steelworkers of America Gr. Nos. A-49-72, A-49-74, A-49-75, A-49-76, A-49-77, A-49-78, A-49-82, A-49-84, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - American Locomotive - Schenectady N.Y. United Steelworkers - Local 2054 Gr. # A-830 11/21/56, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - American Radio Assoc. Vacation Plan 233 Broadway, New York City 5/20/55, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - American Locomotive - Schenectady United Steelworkers - Local 2054 Gr. # A-818 8/29/56, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Capital Airlines, Inc. and District 144 - International Association of Machinists, 1946-1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Blaw-Knox Company - Local 1243 Tool Crib Attendant Grievance 5/25/57, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Baltimore Motor Coach Co. Case File 6/6/52, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - BSC- Baltimore Yard - Local No. 24 Grievance No. 2520, 2651 8/21/52, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Baltimore Motor Coach Company Aasmerce, Division 1300 - A.F.L. Discharge of Drivers 6/6/52, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - BSC - Baltimore Yard - Local 24 Combined Grievances 2497, 2498, 2499, 2500, 1000, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bethlehem Transportation Company United Steelworkers Local No. 5000 Steamer Lackawanna - Neiderrider, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Borden Company - Arbitrator's Opinion and Award, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - BSC - Brooklyn Yard - Local 13 Grievance 575 4/17/52, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - BSC - Brooklyn Yard - Local 13 Grievances No. 559, 560, 561, 563, 564, 565, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Blaw-Knox Company - Local 1243 Code Welders Grievances 5/25/51, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Blaw-Knox Company - Local 1243 Lunch Period Grievance 5/25/51, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America Park Works - Local 1276 - Case No. 791 8/31/50, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Capital Transit: AAOF S&ER&MCE of a Grievance of Cicchini & Pohost 6/29/54, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Courier-Journal & Louisville Times Louisville Newspaper Pressmen's #19 Appeal from Award of Wm. M. Hepburn, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Columbia & Southern Chemical Co. International Chemical Workers New Martinsville, West Va. (6-25-54), 1954 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co vs. Communication Workers of America 6/16/52, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration between; International Association of Machinists and Capital Airlines, Inc. Part 1, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration between; International Association of Machinists and Capital Airlines Part 2, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Capital Airlines International Association of Machinists 3/7/60, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - International Association of Machinists and Capital Airlines (Nat'l Med. Board), 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America Sanderson-Halcomb Works - Local 1277 10/25/50, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America Spaulding Works - Local No. 1339 5/2/51, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America Spaulding Works - Local 2194 - Case No. 1817 & 1818 9/1/1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America Spaulding Works - Local 2194 Case No. 1928 8/31/50, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America Park Works - Local 3432 - Case No. 76 08/14/50, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America Park Works - Local 3432 - Case No. 75 8/14/50, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America Park Works - Local 1276 - Case 780 8/14/50, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Detroit Steel Corp. - Portsmouth Div. Local 2116 - Grievance No. D-1081 12/19/53 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - United Telephone Workers of Delaware and Diamond State Telephone Company, 1953-1958 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Union Exhibit No. D; Collective Bargaining Agreement '57-'58, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration between, Detroit Steel Corporation Portsmouth Division, and United Steelworkers of America C.I.O. Local Union No. 2116, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - American Bridge Company Ambridge Plant, and United Steelworkers of America, C.I.O., Local Union No. 1270 Arbitration Proceedings 8/4/50, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - International Association of Machinists and Capital Airlines, Inc., in re Dart Engine Test Cell, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical Corp. United Steelworkers #329 and #338 Right to Combine jobs under Article 4, 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hughes Tool Company, 1950-1952 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hughes Tool Company - Independent Metal Workers Union, Local No. 2 Decision Issued January 28, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Arbitrator's Opinion & Award Harbison - Walker Refractories General Refractories Company North American Refractories Company, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Evening Star Newspaper Co. (Washington Publishers Association) Columbia Typographical Union No. 101., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - L.F. Grammes and Sons, Incorporated United Steelworkers # AAA L-24486-Phi-L-190-59, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation Case No. 68, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Evening Star Newspaper Company - Washington Newspaper Guild 6/3/58, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 Grievance No. E-115, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation - No. 3116 6/12/52, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - Company Exhibits (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - UTWD - "Rebut" to Mr. Seward's Statement of Fact, 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration between, United Telephone Workers of Delaware and Diamond State Telephone Company Folder #1, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration between, United Telephone Workers of Delaware and Diamond State Telephone Company Folder #2, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Diamond State Telephone Company United Telephone Workers of Delaware, 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Full Fashioned Hosiery Manufacturers of America, Inc. 1/30/52, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Kaiser Steel Corporation - Fontana United Steelworkers Local 2869 Grievance No. 57224 9/24/58, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Kelly-Springfield Tire & Rubber Co. Case No. 2-37-52 7/15/53, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Kelly-Springfield Tire and Rubber Company - Case No. 2-38 and 2-39-52, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Kelly-Springfield Tire Company Case No. 13-52, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Kelly Springfield Tire Company Case No. 9-52, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - E.J. Lavino Company U.S. Steelworkers of America Grievance No. 22-58 (AAA Case), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Kaiser Steel Corporation - Fontana United Steelworkers Local 2869 Grievance Noi. 57140 9/16/58, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kaiser Steel Corporation - Fontana United Steelworkers Local 2869 Grievance No. 57471 9/15/58, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kaiser Steel Corporation - Fontana United Steelworkers Local 2869 Grievance No. 57227 9/10/58, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kaiser Steel Corporation - Fontana United Steelworkers Local 2869 Grievance No. 57260 9/9/58, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kaiser Steel Corporation - Fontana United Steelworkers Local 2869 Grievance No. 5704 9/5/58, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Link-Belt Company (Phila.) United Steelworkers, Local #3828 Grievance No. N-186 (4-30-54), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Mackintosh-Hemphill Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - The W.L. Maxson Corporation United Automobile Workers #1221 Grievance No. 1449 AAA Case No. L-24935-Phi-L-265-59, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Miller & Hart - United Packinghouse Workers - Case Discharge of Willie Shaw 10/16/52, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - New York Photo-Engravers & Publishers Association Fact Finding Recommendation 11/18/53, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - The National Supply Company Arbitrator's Award - December 8, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - The National Supply Company (Ambridge Plant) - Steelworkers Local No. 1360 - Grievance No. 58, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - The National Supply Company Arbitrator's Award - March 9, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - The National Supply Company (Etna Plant) - Steelworkers Local No. 1244 Grievance No. 319, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Publisher's Exhibits; Pittsburgh Newspapers vs. Pittsburgh Mailers Union No. 22, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration Between Pittsburgh Newspaper Guild; Pitt. Newspaper Alliance; Press Circulation Guild; International Association of Machinists and Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, Pittsburgh Sun-Telegraph, and Pittsburgh Press, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh Steel Company - Local 1229 Grievance No. 1453 8/22/52, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits Cases # 333-A, 332-A, M-75, M-77, 1440, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits Cases # 1448, 1445, 1449, 1476, 1464, 1525 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits Cases # 1536-1555, 1463, 1438 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Pittsburgh Bolt and Screw United Steelworkers Local - 1848 Gr. #110, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers American Newspaper Guild Case and Record 10/21/52, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Unions' Exhibits, 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Pittsburgh Steel Co. - Local 1229 Grievance No.s 332-A, 333-A, M-75, 1438, 1440, 1445, 1448, 1449, 1464, 1476, 1525, 1536 & 1555, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, Pittsburgh Press & Pittsburgh Sun-Telegraph vs. Pittsburgh Newspaper Guild, et al., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Pittsburgh Bolt and Screw United Steelworkers - Local 1848 Gr. No. 11-52, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Pittsburgh Bolt and Screw United Steelworkers - Local 1848 Gr. #. 58, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pittsburgh Bolt and Screw United Steelworkers - Local 1848 Gr. # 73, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Pittsburgh Bolt and Screw United Steelworkers Local 1848 Gr. #. 68-69, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Union Employers Division of Printing Industry of Washington Columbia Typographical Union # 101 Discharge Case, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pittsburgh Steel Company Thomas Division - USA, Local 3523 Case No. M-37, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh Steel Company - Thomas Division - USA, Local 3523 Case No. P-32 1/18/52, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh Steel Company - Local 1229 United Steelworkers of America Case No. 1453 7/19/51 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Owl Drug Company Et Al. Retail Clerks Union Local #770 Wage Rates - Pharmacists and Clerks, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Greyhound Lines Hearing 8/20/52, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Greyhound Lines Case File, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - REM-CRU Titanium, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local #5047 Grievance No. 49, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sub Case 1957; Companies' Exhibits (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Union Exhibits, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Indiana Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sub Case - Post Decision Material, 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Final Draft - Sub Case, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - SUB (U.S. Steel Corporation Inland Steel Company Youngstown Sheet & Tube Co. Continental Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America) Supplemental Recommendation - 6/29/59, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Sub Case, 1957 Comp. Exhibits (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - SUB Case, 1957 Union Exhibits (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Sheffield Division - ArmCo. Steel Corp. United Steelworkers #2708 Grievance No. H-58-24-A, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Sheffield Division- ArmCo Steel Corp. United Steelworkers #2708 Grievances No. H-58-26-A, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sheffield Division- ArmCo Steel Corp. United Steelworkers #2708 Grievance No. 339, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sheffield Steel - Houston United Steelworkers Local 2708 4. Grievances. No numbers 6/7/56, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sheffield Steel - Houston United Steelworkers - Local 2708 Grievance No. 15, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sheffield Steel, Div. ArmCo. Steel Corp., Houston, Texas, and United Steelworkers 7/15/55 hearing, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - A. O. Smith Corporation United Steelworkers #4446 James V. Williams Discharge Case 11/29/59, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - A. O. Smith Corporation United Steelworkers #4446 Finish Line Dept. - Work Jurisdiction 11/25/59, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Swift & Company - Local 106 Grievance No. Arbitration No. 307, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SUB Case, 1957 Recommendation Drafts (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Company Various Decisions - 1944 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Swift & Company - Harrisonburg, Va. Case No. 2, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Swift & Company -Local No. 28 Arbitration No. 308 1/25/52, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Swift & Company Local No. 28 Grievance No. 1418 - Arb. No. 305, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Swift & Company Local No. 28 Grievance No. 1395 Arb. No. 304, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Swift & Company - Local 266 Grievance No. 51 - Arb. No. 303, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Swift & Company - Local # 266 -m Arbitration No. 302 - Grievance No. 50, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Swift & Company and Int. Brotherhood of Teamsters, A.F.L. Hearing Date 11/14/55, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Swift & Company - United Construction Workers - Clarine Bush - Arb. #1, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Swift & Company - Local No. 28 Grievance No. Arb. No. 309, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Swift & Company - Local No. 28 Grievance No. 1388 - Arb. No. 306, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Swift & Co. - Local 28 Arbitration No. 301 - Discrimination 11/7/51, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Swift & Co - Harrisonburg, Virginia Case No. 1, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Swift & Company Plant Arb. No. 300 - Grievance No. 1352, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Swift & Company, Inc. I.B.T. Local No. 757 Discharges of Seymour Kaye and Louis La Bruvere, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Swift & Company - Plankinton Plant Arb. No. 299 - Grievance No. 1341, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Swift & Company - Plankinton Plant Arb. No. 298 - Grievance No. 205, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Swift & Company - Plankinton Plant Arb. No. 297 - Grievance No. 84, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Swift & Co. - Centerville Plant Local 435 - Cases 1-A & 6-A, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. Air Line Dispatchers Association Replacement of Foreign-Based Dispatchers by Foreign Nationals 7/18/58, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. International Assn. of Machinists 142 Grievance No. 8670, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. International Assn. of Machinists 142 Grievance No. 12113, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. International Assn. of Machinists 142 Grievances No. 12346, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. International Assn. of Machinists 142 Grievance No. 10161, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. International Assn. of Machinists 142 Grievance No. 17067, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. International Association of Machinists, District Lodge #142 Qualification Protest - G.H. Grabb, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Trans ?World Airlines, Inc. International Assn. of Machinists Grievance No. 19427, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Trans World Airline, Inc. International Assn. of Machinists Grievance No. 16901, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - United Airlines IAM - Airline Employees District 141, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - United States Steel Inequity Case, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Washington Publishers Association Washington Photo-Engravers Union #17 Eligibility for Sick Leave, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Washington (D.C.) Publishers Ass'n and Columbia Typographical Union 101 Re: Al Halpin Discharge. Heard, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Washington Publishers Assoc. & Columbia Typographical Union #101 heard 1/18/56, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Washington Publishers' Assoc. and Columbia Typographical Union, 9/9/55, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Washington Publishers' Assoc. and Mailers' Union No. 29 6/10/55, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - WTOP, Inc. and AFTRA (Paul Wills) heard 7/9/56, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Washington Newspaper Pub. Assoc. Mailers Union No. 29 of Washington D.C. 3-9-55, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Youngstown Sheet & Tube Co: USA - Local 1011 - I-46-50 & I-47-50, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Yale & Towne Manufacturing Company Stanley R. Stokes Discharge Case, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wisconsin Steel (Int. Harvester) Progressive Steel Workers Case Heard 6-16, 17, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - The Youngstown Sheet & Tube Co. USA - Local 1011 - Case No. I-69-50, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The Youngstown Sheet & Tube Co. - USA - Local 1011 - Case No I-68-50, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Youngstown Sheet & Tube Co. Indiana Harbor Plant - Grievance No. I-77-50, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Employer's Exhibits - Mr. Ralph Seward, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Retail Drug Agreement, 1956-1961 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Union Exhibits, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Wage Case (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration between, The Retail Drug Industry and Retail Clerks Union, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - So. Calif. Retail Clerks Unions 1959 Drug Store Arbitration Union Brief and Reply - Mr. Seward's Copies (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Retail Drug Stores vs. Retail Clerks, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - New York Photo-Engravers Union vs. Publishers Association of New York City, 1947-1949 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ralph T. Seward Misc. Papers., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Photo-Engravers Union, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Acme Steel Co. Local No. 1053 Grievance No. A69, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - General Motors Corporation Cost-of-Living Formula, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration between Retail Clerks Union Locals 137, 324, 770, 899, 905, 1167, 1222, 1428 and 1442 of Southern Calif. - vol. 1, 1959 (Box 11.1, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration between Retail Clerks Union Locals 137, 324, 770, 899, 905, 1167, 1222, 1428 and 1442 of Southern Calif. - vol. 2, 1959 (Box 11.1, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration between Retail Clerks Union Locals 137, 324, 770, 899, 905, 1167, 1222, 1428 and 1442 of Southern Calif. - vol. 3, 1959 (Box 11.1, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration between Retail Clerks Union Locals 137, 324, 770, 899, 905, 1167, 1222, 1428 and 1442 of Southern Calif. - vol. 4, 1959 (Box 11.1, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration between Retail Clerks Union Locals 137, 324, 770, 899, 905, 1167, 1222, 1428 and 1442 of Southern Calif. - vol. 5, 1959 (Box 11.1, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration between Retail Clerks Union Locals 137, 324, 770, 899, 905, 1167, 1222, 1428 and 1442 of Southern Calif. - vol. 6, 1959 (Box 11.1, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration between Retail Clerks Union Locals 137, 324, 770, 899, 905, 1167, 1222, 1428 and 1442 of Southern Calif. - vol. 7, 1959 (Box 11.1, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration between Retail Clerks Union Locals 137, 324, 770, 899, 905, 1167, 1222, 1428 and 1442 of Southern Calif. - vol. 8, 1959 (Box 11.1, Folder 8)
- Series II: Arbitration Cases, International Harvester
  - International Harvester: Platt Decisions, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 156 Decision No. 194 - Case EM-0-5, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 157 Decision No. 193 - Case 3-205-C, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 157 Decision No. 192 - Case 1-122-C, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 191 - Case 15590-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 Decision No. 190 - Case FE-324, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 Decision No. 189 - Case FE-288, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 Decision No. 188 - Case FE-309, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 157 Decision No. 187 - Case 6-150-C, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 186 - Case 747-T, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 185 - Case 5769-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 184 - Case A-698-R (B-208), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 183 - Case A-335-R (B-126), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - IHC-Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 180 - Case 3542-A-L, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 182- Case 6528-A-L, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 181 - Case 5719-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 179 - Case No. A-755-R (E-64), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 178 - Case 16052 EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 18)